Growing up my parents had
this insane rule If you
can reach it you clean
it thought it was the
dumbest thing ever
Like I'm supposed to dust
the top of the fridge
I can barely see up
there
Fast forward to adulthood and
I'm living with Chad
Chad who thinks a dirty
dish magically teleports to the
dishwasher
One day I’m cleaning and
find a literal biohazard experiment
growing in the back of
the fridge
I unleash my inner child
climb onto the counter and
start scrubbing like my allowance
depends on it
Chad walks in sees me
precariously perched wielding a sponge
like a weapon and says
Whoa what are you doing
I yell down If you
can reach it you clean
it Chad
IT’S THE LAW
Then he looks at me
dumbfounded
He then asks why I’m
suddenly so clean oriented
I pause
Then I hear a voice
in my head because if
you can’t do chores what
makes you think you can
do schoolwork and then the
video cuts